Carlos (Kalle) Ferraz

Full-stack web dev and Growth, Product, Business dev

Work Experience



Freelance Growth consultant - Doppelhaus (Germany & UK) - July 2020 to present

Consultant on growth, business development, and sales, and as an independent pair of eyes on business strategy for the founders.

Artify Ou/Uku Estonia - Head of Business

development and growth - Oct 2020 to July 2021

Head of business development. All international inbound sales leads, outbound, and determining the strategy for these markets and penetration.

An integral part of the growth team, planning strategy, and implementing experimental ideas to drive growth, measurement, and adjustment. Client research and customer success management on occasion too.



Credo Sales & Marketing Management -

Managing Growth/Founder Nordic countries – based in Finland - 2006 to 2020

As a freelancer, I have taken new products to market in the Nordics, from introducing them to the markets to managing the supply chain.

This also gives a solid basis for negotiations with clients and building long-lasting customer relationships.

A strategy to boost engagement. Increasing revenue through LTV, CTR, and SEO and off-page SEO based on annual KPIs. I also had P&L responsibility for the ongoing contracts, sales plans, reporting, and bimonthly adjustments.

Contact Info



https://github.com/CarlosLF1



www.linkedin.com/in/carlos-ferraz-b205331

- carloslf@e.email
- +358 40 1712418

Tech Stack

SaaS environment and product.

HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React, MongoDB, Express, NodeJS, Git, GitHub, Styled components, and many others.

My current learning map: -

Flutter/Dart, React Native, Figma and UI/UX design.

Tools for understanding -

Toggle, Trello, Jira, Slack, Discord.

Education History



Master's in business administration studies, Business School Netherlands.

Certification – Full Stack Web & App development – WBS coding school Germany. Dec 17 completion.



Certifications/courses – HTML, CSS, JavaScript, CRO, Scrum for developers (LinkedIn and Codecademy)

Professional Groups & Hobbies

- Guest lecturer at the
 International Hotel School on Sales and Marketing.
- Freelance writer for the Portuguese Metal Magazine called the "World of Metal"

https://worldofmetalmag.com

- Rock/metal band
- Ongoing learning and coding growth.

Profile overview



Growth specialist with an excellent integrated online and offline approach. Experience in growing my customer's the client/user base and bottom-line revenues.

I am now transitioning into a **web developer** with the MERN stack and a yearning for ongoing and **continuous learning**. Strong understanding of the user journey and interactions. I am currently a junior **developer** but have an excellent **business** understanding of the pitch, budget, client relations, and at le method and an open role in product management/owners lip.